export const questionData = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following software could assist someone who cannot use their hands for computer input ?",
    options: [
      "Video conferencing",

      "Speech recognition",

      "Audio digitizer ",

      "Synthesizer"
    ],
    answer: "Speech recognition",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "The software tools that enable a user to interact with a computer for specific purposes are known as ?",
    options: ["Hardware ", "Networked Software", "Shareware", "Applications"],
    answer: "Applications",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following software could assist someone who cannot use their hands for computer input ?",
    options: [
      "Video conferencing",

      "Speech recognition",

      "Audio digitizer ",

      "Synthesizer"
    ],
    answer: "Speech recognition",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "The software tools that enable a user to interact with a computer for specific purposes are known as ?",
    options: ["Hardware ", "Networked Software", "Shareware", "Applications"],
    answer: "Applications",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following software could assist someone who cannot use their hands for computer input ?",
    options: [
      "Video conferencing",

      "Speech recognition",

      "Audio digitizer ",

      "Synthesizer"
    ],
    answer: "Speech recognition",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "The software tools that enable a user to interact with a computer for specific purposes are known as ?",
    options: ["Hardware ", "Networked Software", "Shareware", "Applications"],
    answer: "Applications",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following software could assist someone who cannot use their hands for computer input ?",
    options: [
      "Video conferencing",

      "Speech recognition",

      "Audio digitizer ",

      "Synthesizer"
    ],
    answer: "Speech recognition",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "The software tools that enable a user to interact with a computer for specific purposes are known as ?",
    options: ["Hardware ", "Networked Software", "Shareware", "Applications"],
    answer: "Applications",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following software could assist someone who cannot use their hands for computer input ?",
    options: [
      "Video conferencing",

      "Speech recognition",

      "Audio digitizer ",

      "Synthesizer"
    ],
    answer: "Speech recognition",
    rotate: false
  },
  {
    question:
      "The software tools that enable a user to interact with a computer for specific purposes are known as ?",
    options: ["Hardware ", "Networked Software", "Shareware", "Applications"],
    answer: "Applications",
    rotate: false
  }
];
